export const Questions = [
  {
    prompt: "When is my birthday?",
    optionA: "05/01/1994",
    optionB: "05/02/1994",
    optionC: "05/01/1993",
    optionD: "05/02/1995",
    answer: "optionA",
  },
  {
    prompt: "What is my favorite colour?",
    optionA: "Black",
    optionB: "White",
    optionC: "Blue",
    optionD: "Pink",
    answer: "optionD",
  },
  {
    prompt: "What is my favorite special day?",
    optionA: "Christmas",
    optionB: "Halloween",
    optionC: "Valentine's Day",
    optionD: "Thanksgiving",
    answer: "optionB",
  },
  {
    prompt: "What is my first degree on?",
    optionA: "accounting",
    optionB: "marketing",
    optionC: "finance",
    optionD: "civil engineering",
    answer: "optionC",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Who would I not bitch about?",
    optionA: "Someone who is always late",
    optionB: "Someone who believes in astrology",
    optionC: "Someone who is obsessed with fitness",
    optionD: "Someone who does not respond after reading the message",
    answer: "optionC",
  },
  {
    prompt:
      "Which one of the options was not part of Kelly's 2023 new year goal",
    optionA: "Becoming patient",
    optionB: "Actually date someone",
    optionC: "Another co-op in a company that provides mac for developers",
    optionD: "Becoming less obsessed with fitness",
    answer: "optionD",
  },
  {
    prompt: "What type of flower is Kelly's favorite",
    optionA: "Light pink roses",
    optionB: "Light pink peonies",
    optionC: "Light pink dahlias",
    optionD: "Light pink tulips",
    answer: "optionB",
  },
  {
    prompt: "What is not a factor that Kelly cares about in a guy?",
    optionA: "car",
    optionB: "career ambition",
    optionC: "sanity",
    optionD: "niceness",
    answer: "optionA",
  },
  {
    prompt: "What activities would constitute as the perfect Sunday?",
    optionA:
      "Wake up late -> workout -> cofee&brunch -> farmer's market -> go home and chill",
    optionB:
      "Wake up early -> workout -> cofee&brunch -> farmer's market -> go home and chill",
    optionC:
      "Wake up late -> workout -> cofee&brunch -> eaton center -> go home and chill",
    optionD:
      "Wake up late -> workout -> mimosa&brunch -> farmer's market -> go home and chill",
    answer: "optionA",
  },
  {
    prompt:
      "How many days per week does Kelly think is the perfect quantity to meet her partner?",
    optionA: "1/7",
    optionB: "2/7",
    optionC: "3/7",
    optionD: "4/7",
    answer: "optionB",
  },
];
